[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Can a frontrunner Mitt Romney now break out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "It sure is nice to have a win.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What do you put that down to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Do you believe the real battleground will move on to South Carolina and to Florida?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "You know, I think the odds-makers would probably bet that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina", "Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Are you surprised that, say, Rick Perry is staying in the race, given how he's underperformed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I haven't concentrated on what he should do or being surprised or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "But as more scrutiny comes on him now, do you think he'll be able to withstand the inevitable media attention that he will now get for what many would say are policies which in some cases go to the more extreme right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, you know, my criticism isn't that he's an extreme conservative.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "How did you react when he called you disgusting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "I'm sorry, I missed that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Is it time that this election gets real and inevitably gets ugly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Yes, and it's probably the part of politics I never liked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "How do you change perception to make people believe you could seriously be president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, you know, I get a charge out of this when they say that these views are extreme and that -- I wouldn't be elected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Do you want to apologize for telling me that you found his one Iowa voter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "CD", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, you know, that was done, you know, through staff.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["75 percent"]}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "That, I would imagine, gives you more hope, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Oh, listen, it was -- Piers, it was a wonderfully ambiguous outcome, when you had 75 percent of those casting a vote that decided not to listen to the person the establishment is teeing up on a silver platter, Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What is the yardstick that we should be using to judge Huntsman's success in New Hampshire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, listen, we've gone from dead last place to what the most recent polls, including one of yours, had put us in the teens today at third place.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Huntsman"], "LOCATION": ["New Hampshire"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "How are you going to brand yourself in a simple-to-understand way that differentiates you from Mitt Romney and surging Rick Santorum as he's now known?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "There's only way to brand yourself, and that is based upon your record, what you have done, where you've been and what you offer the American people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan"]}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "But do you think that alignment with a Democratic president has harmed you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Listen, I worked for President Reagan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Will you fight fire with fire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "When we look at what's coming up primary-wise, what are the key places, do you think, the key battle grounds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Certainly South Carolina is going to be potentially decisive for them in their field.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wasserman Schultz"]}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "So he goes on having won the first two battles, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, first off, what I heard from Congresswoman Wasserman Schultz is that they're worried about Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, I think we have a real problem in this country relative to campaign finance, which was created by people who tried to reform campaign financing in the word -- for the purposes of doing good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What do you make of the fact that it was so close and that Santorum came from nowhere to get as far as he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, I think Bob Vander Plaats really helped.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "And does Santorum represent now, do you think, the core traditional values of the Republicans, perhaps better than any other candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Well, he really is a very conservative guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What does that tell you, Donald, about Mitt Romney's standing with his own party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, I think he did a very good job, though, Piers, no matter how you cut it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Can any other candidate really compete in a modern political battle against someone like Romney, given the resources he has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Well, I guess the answer is yes, because I've watched him go up and down like yo-yos, everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "So what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "First of all, I do like her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "And do you think he will now change strategy because he has no choice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Well I think he is now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Am I misreading the lines here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Yes, I think you are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]